Hey Allu Arjun Welcome back to my channel's
printing Friends, in today's first video
we did weekly market flats,
see all the important indicators and as
you saw in that video, right now the market has
got a lot of bullish momentum, so we
feel that this is the time to be a little careful and a little
cautious Keeping all these news and events in
mind, which are the
fundamentals that are interesting to you,
which are still available to you at good valuations
and at which price level can you buy them, we will
discuss that in this video, so
before starting the video, let me tell you that
if you have not subscribed to the channel till now, then
this is a machine law to give information and it was about to
invest in animals,
patients. Your likes and comments on your subjects give
me more motivation and I keep
trying to get videos on your suggestion, Kevat Officer too Don't forget to press the subscribe button
subscribe The Channel and friend notification
button so that
you do not miss any of the upcoming videos  Don't miss it. You can
also follow us on Facebook, Twitter, and Telegram
to enhance your knowledge and improve your anxiety. The
links are given in the description. So,
without taking any more time, let's
start friends. Our first
stock exchange today is about the difficult market market of general insurance.
ICICI Lombard is
also known as Disstabilized General Insurance.
Before the discussion, let me
tell you that here we will
not discuss the debt fund mental balance of all the staff.
Otherwise, this video will become very long.
For fundamental analysis, I will
make separate videos for all these staff of
HDFC Bank. I have already made a separate
video for it. I have detailed its finance quotes, messages, Jyoti Doob history, a lot of it, I have done it wisely. Like that video. I am
putting it in a bowl so that
you can easily check that information.
But this video is for that purpose.
Here we are going to pre-register all the staff.
What kind of staff are these? At what
price are you getting them?
At what valuation?  It is available and we will cover some basic
metrics here but
for the date fundamental analysis of all, I will
create video of every clip,
so advisor, we said that
in the general insurance sector, there is medical player, the
shine of private players
is the biggest player, the best script is Middle East,
if we talk about some of its basic metrics, then the
market capitalization is around
55,000 crores around 57
thousand crores, around vague point
percent which is on the lower
side, but you must have seen the growth prospects of
finance from many quarters that
they have not increased by one and a half times, they are
reserving their capital, Punjab,
because in the times to come, there is
some answer for the financial industry,
hence you will see in financial stocks
that the search love is a little less in the current
situation, but in future, if the fundamentals of that company are
strong with the market leader, then
I believe that you can also go and
join them, that too can be handsome, son, if we
talk about it, then whoever watches our videos on pan
Look, for those who did not return ours, I will
revise it once because son, this is a
network which shows
how much that particular stock is below the overall market,
whether it is high voltage or low
voltage. Now, if it were less than beta-1, then we would assume that
that particular stock would be slightly below the market.
And when it were more than beta-1, then we would
assume that this stock would be higher than the market. So
let's take a look at the
beta. You can see that this point note is
slightly below the market. The
industry speed is between 2849 and
you are getting it at a slight premium valuation.
But on that validation and this
market price also, you can see
how strong the delivery is.
I ask for the number very quickly, and it is above the delivery of 3040 China. And this is a
degree of sixty-five percent. This
shows how much confidence people have
in Allahabad's stock for long term
investment. How many people are taking delivery of the cabinet
in their long term investment account and
long term interest account. The
price of this  If you
look at the labels, if you
get it between 1225 and 1250, then this can be a very
handsome level for your initial
investment. But if you
want to wait a little and for the near term and do a little
work, if you get even 1111 hundred and fifty, then
that can also be a very good
level. It can be very good
for the long-term industry. For
example, ITC
is a new player in Fancy G. Its brand is
still evolving. Some brands have gained a
good hold behind, but some brands are
still creators, so due to this it is
not considered a complete important CG player. It is
considered a primary cigarette player
because you must be aware that in the cigarette market in
India, a slight AB to every
five percent market is there, so it is
considered a primary cigarette player.
Because of this, you are seeing that the valuation of the thing will be
so strong, but the kind of
brand it is creating, the kind of
positive karma it has, which is the
vacancies of the cigarette business.  It uses it this way,
requests from there and
destroys all the other segments of Saif's last business paper, hotels, so its branding and
Shivji's branding is gradually increasing.
It is cleaning up its image a bit. This
process may take
some time, but if you have patience,
ITC can be a very
strong candidate for investment.
I believe that in the future,
people will accept the SSC business and will do college,
and its daughter can be in terms of
SSC, but not in terms of cigarettes. So this
shot background subscribe my channel Lakh Crore
Ke Upar, so you subscribe channel
subscribe 602, this is much less than the market,
hence you can see very less, but the
subscription is a little more than the market,
30.78 of the industry, subscribe here, so what
you are seeing is, I think it is
PM of the cigarette industry, so as I
said, it is also considered as a cigarette black market,
whereas it has many businesses, one is
agri business, one is Suji, hotel complex.
Everyone, even in the IT business, so
if you compare the industries of the cigarette business, then the
peer industries of 130 are
1340 because you have a very strong delivery percentage of its
compatible payment friend 57
percent,
this shows that a lot of people are
taking delivery of it, address market
is the latest market price,
if this trick gives you the current price juice, then
16573 is in the middle, so the 16573 level is not a very
attractive level, I do not think so
for the near to short-term, and if you want to
wait for the long term and if you are
not comfortable reaching this price level, then
you can wait for the level of 135 to 160, at
that level, wisdom comes, it can be clearly
unattractive, for long term
investment,
I see it as a very good candidate,
yes, ma'am, father for and chemical business and that
industry can be a very good play,
another video in which we
discussed the best option for healthcare industry, so follow the museum, I had given
input on that.  The discussion was a bit long,
so let me tell you
that for Zee, the glass line recruitment
business of India, which
also creates the pharma business and
competes with the chemical business, is a company that serves both of these specifically.
It is the market leader in India
in parlor-exempt glass line equipment.
Now its
market share is around 500 percent.
It has
acquired DS, and then Ford and its
parent company is also doing well.
If we take into account the signals, then
between 6 months to a year, I think its
market share can reach 832 percent.
Therefore, I think this can be a very
good business. For the long term, it
is a market leading business
in your sector. In fact,
you can see that these shortcut companies have a
market of around Rs 5000 crore. So, it is a market leader in the
small cap companies and the
prisoners sector in which it works.
That business segment is
small, but within that segment.  If it is
marketed internally, then you should share it with the market.
Fundamentally, it
seems to me that the promoters have
no problem in saying yes, so it
shows you whether their intent is to
expand the global business. Its yield is
quite low. Point 140
is an integrated service small cap, so you will see
that the deals of summer camp companies are a little
less, especially in public
sector undertakings. Public sector companies,
private sector companies of small companies,
you will see that the private sector's de
Villiers will be a little less because they
apply the freebies of their colleagues. They do
not do much different for their growth because
friend, Judge R's
Tiffin Software business cycle, so
the invention and surprised and
distributing dividend yield,
you will see it is a little less famous on that, son,
its point note 5a, so it
is almost as volatile as the industry's 12.5, 6, but
you are getting it at a good premium valuation.
You can see one thing on the stomach, but
its female version seems to me to be better and
justified, so it is the
market leader in its sector and its competitors,
their fundamentals are not as strong as
James Potter's, so there is prevention of
course, so you
can also wait for a little price correction, if you feel more
confident about it, then its
valuation will always be a
little expensive as compared to the industry, no matter how much
offer you have received, but still, there will
always be some prevention of it because this
is that kind of business and it is getting
its songs from the computer, so its
valuation will be a little PM, so that is a
design of 3536 percent, quite Edison
Haldi Daily presentation, which shows that
even at this price level, people are taking its delivery
in Haldi way, so if we
talk about the price level, then if you want to wait somewhere between 3450
to 3650, that is, around 2436, then it can be
a good different level, so
start your investment
in 10 top if you want to wait a little.  Yes,
and for the near term and little reason,
if you get a healthy child between 2750, then it is a
very good level and it can be a
small step in it, which has already suffered the impact of its shape, so if you
want to keep a little flat margin in it,
want to wait a little, then the level of 2550 might be
good for you for these 10 minutes.
HDFC Life, the legendary player, Life
Bus, there are many life insurance
papers listed, there are three-four, but
I think the best stock among them is to
take tips because its fundamentals are so
strong, its market capitalization is
around Rs 1 lakh 16 thousand crore,
so it has
not yet declared a dividend, which shows that it is
also focusing on capital conservation and
growth, son, its 1.08
financial sector stocks, so you will have a
little more order type from the market,
so you can see that because of this, there is a
little more industry experience in it
and you are also getting daughters at a little cream
valuation, but on this PM van
also and this market price of  You can see
that the delivery percentage of 69% is very strong and impressive.
It shows how much people believe in it
and how much long-term
potential they see in it. Therefore, if we
talk about the share price level, then the level of 550 to 575 can be
a suitable level for you to
enter. If you want to enter at the top,
if you want to update, then the
level of 500 to 525 can be an attractive
level. If you want to
fold the stop for long-term investors, then
you can take our distraction. This
topic is of Gujarat State Petronet
Limited (BSP). As you can see,
this pipe can go
into the distribution of development. We have talked about
oil
in the earlier videos. Similarly, the
condition of GSPL business is also like Glen Mills
on electricity creation. Its
business is also borderless. As
you will know from the name, its
area of ​​operation is Gujarat and joining
yes, JSPL is a public  It is a sector company,
but despite being a public sector company, it is a
very well-run company. Therefore, if you take a written
test, then look at natural gas,
etc., then you will see
how strong this company is. All its
fundamental parameters are quite good, so that is why
I like it very much. There is a
market application of about 10011 1000 crores,
so this margin
is between small cap and midcap.
Daniel, if we talk about it, then the
copy of 1.04 percent is respectable to a great extent.
Its points to the market, so it is
much lower than the market. The industry's price
is also around 10 and
you are getting almost the same speed on the back. The
industry's base is
very excellent. The turmeric
delivery percentage of 67 percent shows that
people also go for a fall in this topic for the
long term. If we talk about the price level for this, then
1820 levels, the current market price
comes within the back, then that price can be
quite attractive for long term
investment.  If you want to wait a little
and if you get this stock
at 17134 level then that is a very
excellent level factory, it is a company with good fundamentals, it is a
very balanced company, it is a
very good company, you
can select this stock for long term
investment and both of these are
priceless in whichever one you
feel more comfortable in, you can
cancel the investment at that level if
you see good long term potential in this stock
and if you see the
possibility of addition in the long term, then you
can keep both of these in mind first friends, this today's
video is from this inch clear knowledge power shopping
national commission which will bring to you the right knowledge
almanac, in every upcoming video we will
discuss many interesting topics
and I will tell you your used oil idea
shot office, similarly every weekend
we keep discussing weekly market updates and our views
about current market situation, so
definitely subscribe to the
channel and event posted father roti if
you liked your video appointed then the
video  Like it if you think this
information can help someone then
share it with your friends and family members and subscribe to the channel. See you
in our next video
with another topic discussion. Till then take care
and stay tuned.